Hi. Hello guys. Welcome back to Grow
with Lucky YouTube channel. One hospital
bill can destroy your 10 years of
savings. Three lakh, five lakh,
sometimes 10 [music] lakhs also guys.
But a health insurance cost you a less
than Zomato or Swiggy bill. Guys, today
I compared India's top health insurance
companies and one mistake most people
can cost everything. Don't buy any
policy before watching this. So let's
start this video. If any newcomers, new
viewers into my [music] channel, please
hit the like button and share with your
family and friends. So let's start this
video. Imagine this. Sudden surgery
happens. [music] Doctor calls you and
ask you to deposit 10 lakhs. What you
will do guys? [music] Sell your gold or
take a loans or are you going to use
your savings? So this is how middle
class will go broke. Health insurance is
not a luxury, it's a survival. So
[music]
that's the reason most of the people
will choose a cheapest policy but they
are not aware what is the policy [music]
will gives the terms and conditions and
a cheap insurance becomes most expensive
during the claim time guys [music] they
reject claims add limits or they can
delay the payment so don't ask the
cheapest health insurance policy ask
which base it properly. Let's take a
example with the topmost companies which
gives a [music] proper health insurance
on time or not. Star Health and [music]
Allied Insurance this is having a
largest hospital network easy cashless
good for families [music] but premium
slightly higher side. So this might be
best option for family coverages. And
the second one health insurance which is
NAB health insurance fast claim
settlements modern plans no room rent
cap in many plants but very favor
hospital connectivity and this is best
for young work professionals. And the
third one is STFC Erggo Health
Insurance. Trusted brand, [music]
balanced pricing, large hospitality
network and 100% clean, smooth service,
good reviews. This is best for all round
options. And the fourth one, ICIC
Lombard. So it has a strong digital app,
quick approval. Sometimes some some
people might can afford it is in a
costly way but this is a best for tech
friendly users. So what are the terms
and condition before buying a health
insurance policy from all the top of the
companies? Major one 90% ratio of claim
settlement you [music] have to check
before buying a health insurance and the
second one waiting period and the third
one room rent limit and the fourth one
cashless hospital near for you. These
are the four major factor before buying
a health insurance you have to go
through. So what might be your final
recommendation? So I'm not going to tell
that this is the best and this is not
best. So all four are [music] best in
India. So if you are planning to go for
the family [music] insurance.
to might be a star health insurance is a
options and if you are a young
professional you might can choose NEA
bupa a third one a best option you can
[music] choose STFC ergo but the best
insurance policy you have [music] to buy
in the early stage before the disase
comes after disase nobody [music] gives
you any policy There's one drawback in
all over India 90% of the people
never bought any health insurance till
now my strong suggestion go further
buying a health insurance it's a best
choice in your life so comment your age
and budget I will suggest the best
coverage for you personally and share
with your friends and family who are
looking for health insurance [music] so
thank you so much guys for your time. We
will see you on the next